Sup everyone, T35 here with a very
special video today. Now, I'm going to
tell like it is up front cuz I want to
get anything from lying to y'all. This
was the worst episode in the whole
goddamn show by file. I I I actually
consider dropping it halfway through the
episode. I had to get up and walk away
walk away twice and then come back.
That's how bad it was. The episode
starts with Bloom and the Wings Club
leaving school along with the rest of
school, which is basically just like,
you know, six other random students. Is
is this supposed to be the whole school?
Cuz it's it become more and more evident
this show just doesn't got the budget to
fill out a whole entire school. Which
begs the question, why why did they do a
school show in the first place? Like
they didn't need to do that. Anyways,
the goalies are all excited to head to
town and you know what, [__] So am
I. I am too. I want to see what the
magical town of of Magixia. I'm cheating
you. That's really what it's called.
Like I want to see what Magix is all
about. We are told that it's like the
capital of the fairy world and [__]
We're going shopping, [__] Hence the
title, the shopping trip. You know what
it is. And in case the title didn't
already make it obvious, we're heading
into filler territory, [__] It's not
really filler, I guess, cuz some plots
[__] does happen, but you know, you get
to feel when you're getting into filler
territory after you get through the
first half of Yeah. Yeah. That's it.
Wait, wait. Where is the town they're
going to? Cuz the school, as we've been
shown, is in the middle of a bunch of
trees and [__] Like, we're talking
miles away from any other civilization
and [__] But, but when everybody's
leaving the school, they're just walking
out into the forest. Do they got to walk
all the way like 20 miles just to get to
a gas station or a McDonald's? What is
going on here? Professor Griselda comes
out like, "No, you girls are grounded
because you like didn't do your
homework. where you have to catalog
spores of the three main orders. So,
Robin takes them out to force and is
ordered to watch them to make sure, you
know, they do the homework, which
includes studying the spores of of the
orders instead of sneaking off. But
Robin is a real one. She's like, "Nah,
you girls can head into the city, but
don't tell the other teachers about
this." Okay, so this is why I really
don't get. So Bloom and the fairy
[__] they head off and they are
walking by the magical animal farm and
Bloom asked, "How do we get to the
city?" Cuz you know she's a stupid human
and [__] And she was like, "Oh,
you stupid stupid human [__] Watch
this." Portalius magics evoko. She opens
a portal to Magixia. Then why did you
guys go to the animal bound? Why not
just open the portal in front of Robin
when she said you could go instead of
going to the barn at all? This makes me
mad. This makes me mad for some reason.
Why do they walk anywhere in this show?
Like yeah, it answers my question from
the beginning. Why the squ in the middle
of the woods when they can't all just,
you know, like fast travel from location
to location? But then why were all the
fies walking out of the front gates
anyways? Why why into the trees? Why why
don't they just teleport from the dorms?
Are you telling me you can't teleport
from your dorms to to the IHOP? Like you
got to go to the bone or like 30 ft in
front of the school just do it. That
makes me mad and I don't know why. Oh.
Oh. Oh. I I see why they came to the
bone. It It's cuz the Raz needed us to
see Damian again. The ghoul say, "Hey."
And then leave. And then Damen goes into
the bone and out of nowhere Vexus
appears. Like literally like a fart.
Like a gust of wind appears right by
Damian's ass. I thought Damen farted for
a second. Like I thought, damn, Damian,
were you eating beans? But then the
smoke turned into Vexius. And Damian
kneels like a [__] Which I thought was
funny. Vexus hasn't done [__] in the
whole show to warn anyone bowing to his
ass cheeks. If any if anything, he's
making want to do the opposite based off
how he's been throwing his stupid baby
tantrums every episode. Like what's the
opposite of kneeling? Like standing up.
I feel like you could have stood
dominance over him just by standing and
[__] you know? And yeah, and just to
warn y'all, he's not gonna do [__] by
the end of the episode still like
because that's how Vex is. Vex decides
it's time to attack Bloom and steal her
dragon flame once and for all again.
But, you know, not Phil this time like
they did the last time. And and yeah,
he says now is the best time and [__]
cuz they will be away from school, which
I I don't know what he means by that.
The school is empty. So so empty that a
month ago break into the room just two
episodes ago and no security guards or
none in notice and the trickers are
around every corner beating like Bloom
Bloom's ass like shoving her and the
wings into lockers without the teachers
noticing or or even caring. Th this this
school is empty. Like Vexus, you have
been throwing your poopy baby tantrums
all over this school in public. Like out
in the open. Why the fairies do you
think it would be better to attack Bloom
and her little winces at a bustling city
where no doubt hundreds of people? Oh,
okay. Maybe like 10 people based off the
show's budget and they don't got a
background, but but still like all those
people will be there to witness the
whole attack. Like but Damian is like,
"Okay, daddy." Yeah, like I will do it,
daddy. You got it, daddy. But he's like,
"Oh, no, not you. Not you, Damian. The
chicks are gone." You know, cuz they
actually get [__] done. But then, okay,
then why do you come here, Vexis? Like,
why? I don't get I What's going on? We
cut over to Magixia where Bloom is just
having a jolly old time. And you know
what? Because of the show's budget, I
was fully prepared to say the show the
the town of Vixia look like [__] I was
going in with the low expectations. I
was getting ready to show on the wet
look. And you know what, [__] I just
I I just want to say I'm happy to be
proved right cuz this place looks like
hot ass. You could you got glass trees
all over the place and the buildings are
straight up just clipping through the
ground. Oh my god, there are babies just
walking around with floating ice cream
balls and other babies walking around
literally without their parents. Look at
the three-year-old just straight up
walking around full of bloom and her
pack of [__] They're completely
oblivious that they're going to run the
baby over. The kid was probably trampled
to death. So like the boys show up, you
know, the the the specialist Sky,
Brandon, and Riven. I couldn't help but
notice the nerd wasn't there. They left
him at home cuz he would have ruined
their like whole broa. And I thought
that was really funny. Riven says hi to
music and she gets pissed off and walks
look another baby by itself. What is
going on? Oh, and the wings are here too
buying clothes. And Damian is is also
here with a salamander that eats fire.
It It's named Sally and it's going to
eat Bloom's fire. I It was at this point
that I had to take a 10-minute break so
I could get up and go and go poop. But
that 10-minute break actually lasted
like 2 hours because I forgot what I was
doing. And I came back and the Winxes
use magic to turn No, no, not the Wings.
The trick says use magic to turn Sally
into a giant monster Sally to attack the
city. I I don't I didn't get this. Vex
said the whole reason he went to Bloom
attacking the city was so that nobody
would notice. Why did this suddenly
become Godzilla? So everyone's getting
asses beat, right? And Sky runs over
like Bloom this way. There are civilians
who need help and [__] and Bloom goes
over, but it turns out it was just Darcy
in disguise. And it turns out it was
just just bullies being bullies. I I
guess doing what they do with how Bloom
in a corner and she's like, "Bitch, we
know you're not going to the teachers.
Like, what are you going to do, [__]
Call call the professors. Uh-uh. We know
you're too much of a [__] to do that."
I'm going in now. like they're not
getting in trouble again when they got
rid of the school. Time stamp these
[__] You know I'm going to be right.
You know it. We We are the wings. We
light up the night. Together we're
stronger. We're one of a kind. Okay, so
I got to point this out. I noticed
something that I literally don't think
anyone else noticed. Like I looked
around just see and like I'm not saying
I'm the number one Wings Club fan on
Earth or anything, but I generally think
I'm the only one who saw this. Did they
censor the transformation sequences in
like post-prouction and [__] Cuz you
you'll notice that at the start of the
transformation and [__] the girls are
all wearing these sparkly pajamas or
whatever. I guess I don't know what
they're called. Just bear with me for a
second. But you'll notice there are like
these lines right above the waist and
below the chest separating the midriff.
For some characters like Flu and Ma,
it's hard to see because the midriff is
like the same color as the rest of the
outfit and [__] But for others like
Aisha, her midwiff is a darker blue
color and still it's just ever so
slightly like a lot of orange. The
fabric is also much thinner. You could
say like even skin t. But here's the
thing. If you slow down flow sequence
for just a few frames, the midrift piece
actually just straight up disappears
implying that this is probably colored
later in in production and [__] which
is why some characters mid rifts are
darker or louder than they should be.
Like the only possation I can think of
for that is the midrifts were supposed
to be showing all throughout which makes
sense cuz if you notice none of the
wings in the show they never had
clothing covering that out of the body
even in the reboot. The only ones who
don't have the middle of showing are
Aisha and Fa meaning that Musa, Stella,
Techna, and Bloom all lose that piece of
clothing once the transformation is done
and [__] Which begs the question, why
is there at at all why is it there at
all in the transformation sequence?
Like, and the only thing I can think of
is some high up was like, nah, [__]
this is too sexual. We we can't be
showing [__] that that people have
belly buttons and [__] Anyways, that's
that's all. I don't really care. Like, I
just thought it was weird. So Sky and
the Boys show up to Fat Sally, but they
don't do anything. It was here that I
had to take another break from the
episode and I went and made an omelette,
you know, like out of eggs and [__] I
ate my omelette, but I was annoyed the
whole time cuz I knew I was going to
have to go back and watch the wings the
rest of the wings episode. So I went and
took another poop. Like you know how
that's how much I didn't like the
episode. I pooped twice in one day just
cuz I didn't want to go back. So, the
fairy and the witch professors from
school, they show up and they stop Sally
by making her small again and they tell
Bloom and the girls to go to the
principal's office. Oh, here it comes.
Witches, here it comes. The bullies are
getting in trouble again. The bullies
are Oh my god. Oh my god. Far gone or
whatever name it says that as she's
going to take the pals away for for a
week. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god.
This school sucks. And here we are at
the bottom again with Vances here to
throw another one of his baby poopy
tantrums in front of four kids. What are
we doing here? Dead ass. I see Stormy
Dos and Damian are just standing around
and this band is like three times their
age and he is kicking and screaming and
[__] in his diaper. I can smell it.
I can smell it through the screen. Clean
him up. Oh my god. He is pooping in in
his diaper about how how he can't get
blue dragon flame. Okay. Okay. Man, why
don't you do it? You go do it, poopy
baby. Also, Damian sneaks off and
notices he awakened fire magic. You
know, cuz he's obviously going to be
Bloom's evil twin brother and [__]
Subscribe and follow me on Patreon for
more awesome Wings Club reviews and
fairy content. I just realized I didn't
give this episode a score. I'll give it
a one out of 10. It wasn't good. The D
was called Shop the Shopping Trip and
there wasn't any shopping trip at all. I
wish there was. Okay, wait. We're not
actually done yet. I did have to go back
to the original cartoon to see what the
town of Magics look like over there. And
[__] if I didn't tell you that [__]
blew my mind. Back in the original
cartoon, Magic's still look like [__]
But what was what was the point? Like
even even Bloom is like, "This is it,
[__] This is New York. This looks like
where I come from." Cuz remember in the
original Bloom comes from like the
ghetto and [__] which oh my god, this
actually makes more sense than whatever
the Reaper was trying to do when Bloom
showed up and was like, "This is
amazing. Ha. Yeah. Woo.
Woo. And the wigs were all like, "We
know, [__] We know." Like, like they
said that like they really did
something. Oh, and also in New Town
wasn't even called Majixia. It It was
called New Magics. Like, I don't know
why they made that change, but they did.
The This show is confusing. What is even
going on, [__] Well, why is Bloom so
annoyingly happy all the time in this in
the reboot? I'm sorry to realize that.
It's like how how when she first got her
back in the episode one she was
disappointed but in the reboot she was
excited for some reason even though it
was like [__] like Bloom Bloom is like a
clown. Like Bloom Bloom the clown. Like
she's not allowed to be anything other
than happy. She's just a fool. A fool
here to like get excited at everything
because like we the viewers are supposed
to X out of everything. And I guess she,
you know, she's like, "Oh, self-insert,
but it's like we're not th this show is
ugly and it sucks." Like, it's really
weird. That's it. I just want to share
that little power I found. And yeah,
this show is weird as [__] I I don't
know if I'm excited for episode 5. Oh,
wait. No, this is episode 5. Is it?
Yeah. Like, I don't know if I'm excited
for episode 6, but
episode 6 is coming whether I like it or
not.
The seasons come and go like thoughts of
you.
Like a wave returns to the sea into the
blue.
They change but in a cycle
that I can't lose.
each painful but delightful
to live through.
You came into my life just like another
season. Not for long, just a time. Just
like another season. Maybe this time
next year you'll reear for no reason.
But I'll cherish every day until you
find my way this season.
[Music]
The seasons turn and change just like
you're mine.
Like the sun gives into the moon into
the night.
Time continues marching. It slowly
crawls.
With each new one starting,
I recall
you came into my life. Just like another
season. Not for long, just a time. Just
like another season. Maybe this time
next year you'll reappear.